best_FOOD_score 0.87
O O O FOOD-B FOOD-B O 
O O FOOD-B FOOD-B POH-B O 

POH-B POH-I POH-I POH-I POH-B POH-I POH-I POH-I O O FOOD-B O 
POH-B POH-I POH-I ORG-I POH-B ORG-I ORG-I ORG-I O O FOOD-B O 

O O O NOH-B O NOH-B O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O NOH-B O O O O O O 
O O O NOH-B O NOH-B O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O NOH-B O O O FOOD-B O O 

O NOH-B NOH-I O O FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B O NOH-B FOOD-B FOOD-B O O O FOOD-B FOOD-B O O O O 
O NOH-B O O O FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B O NOH-B FOOD-B O O O FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B O O O O 

LOC-B LOC-I O O PER-B NOH-B O O O O FOOD-B FOOD-B O O 
LOC-B LOC-B O O PER-B NOH-B O O O O FOOD-B FOOD-B O O 

DUR-B O O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O POH-B POH-I O O O O O O O FOOD-B O 
DUR-B O O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O POH-B O O O O O O O O FOOD-B O 

POH-B O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O ORG-B O O O O O O O O 
ORG-B O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O ORG-B O O ORG-B O O O O O O O O 

O O FOOD-B NOH-B O O 
O O FOOD-B O O NOH-B 

POH-B O O FOOD-B O O O O 
POH-B O LOC-B FOOD-B O O O O 

POH-B POH-I POH-I O O O O O FOOD-B 
POH-B POH-I POH-B O O O O O FOOD-B 

O O O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O O NOH-B NOH-I O O O O O O O NOH-B NOH-I O O O 
O O O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O O NOH-B NOH-I O O O NOH-B O O O NOH-B NOH-I O O O 

PER-B FOOD-B FOOD-I O O O FOOD-B O FOOD-B O FOOD-B O FOOD-B FOOD-I O 
PER-B FOOD-B FOOD-I O O O FOOD-B O FOOD-B O FOOD-B POH-I FOOD-I FOOD-I O 

O DAT-B O O O FOOD-B O O O O DUR-B NOH-B O ORG-B O O FOOD-B 
O DAT-B O FOOD-B O FOOD-B O O O O DUR-B NOH-B O ORG-B O O FOOD-B 

FOOD-B O MNY-B O MNY-B FOOD-B O MNY-B O MNY-B FOOD-B O MNY-B O O 
FOOD-B O MNY-B O MNY-B FOOD-B O MNY-B O MNY-B POH-B O MNY-B O O 

POH-B POH-I O NOH-B FOOD-B O O O O O O NOH-B O O O 
FOOD-B ORG-B O NOH-B O O O O O O O NOH-B O O O 

O O FOOD-B O O O O O LOC-B LOC-I O ORG-B O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O 
O O FOOD-B O O O O O LOC-B LOC-B O LOC-B O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O 

PER-B PER-I O MNY-B O FOOD-B O O O O ORG-B O O O 
PER-B O O MNY-B O FOOD-B O O O O ORG-B O O O 

POH-B PER-B O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O O 
O PER-B O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O O 

O PER-B O DAT-B ORG-B POH-B POH-I O FOOD-B FOOD-I FOOD-I O O O O O O 
O PER-B O DAT-B POH-B POH-B POH-I O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O O O O O O 

O FOOD-B DAT-B DAT-I ORG-B O ORG-B O O O NOH-B O NOH-B O O O O O O 
O FOOD-B DAT-B DAT-I LOC-B O ORG-B O O O NOH-B O NOH-B O O O O O O 

FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B O O O O O O DAT-B O 
O O O O FOOD-B FOOD-B O O O O O O DAT-B O 

FOOD-B O O O O ORG-B O O O 
FOOD-B O O O O LOC-B O O O 

FOOD-B FOOD-I O FOOD-B FOOD-I PER-B O O O O O O O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O 
FOOD-B O O POH-B POH-I PER-B O O PER-B O O O O O POH-B O O 

ORG-B O DAT-B POH-B FOOD-B O O O 
ORG-B O DAT-B O FOOD-B O O O 

O O O FOOD-B PNT-B O FOOD-B PNT-B O FOOD-B PNT-B O FOOD-B PNT-B O 
POH-B O O FOOD-B PNT-B O FOOD-B PNT-B O O PNT-B O O PNT-B O 

ORG-B O DAT-B O O O O O O O NOH-B O FOOD-B O NOH-B NOH-B DAT-B FOOD-B O NOH-B O 
ORG-B O O O O O O O O O NOH-B O FOOD-B O NOH-B NOH-B O FOOD-B O NOH-B O 

O O O O FOOD-B FOOD-B O FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-I O 
O O O O FOOD-B FOOD-B O FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-I FOOD-I O 

FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O O O 
FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O 

DAT-B O O O PER-B FOOD-B O O O 
DAT-B O O FOOD-B PER-B FOOD-B O O O 

