best_FOOD_score 0.87
O O O O FOOD-B O O O O 
O O O O FOOD-B O O O O 

O O O O O FOOD-B O 
O O O O O FOOD-B O 

O FOOD-B ORG-B O O O O O O 
O FOOD-B ORG-B O O O O O O 

FOOD-B O FOOD-B FOOD-B O 
FOOD-B O FOOD-B FOOD-B O 

FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O 
FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O 

O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O 
O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O 

O O O O FOOD-B O 
O O O O FOOD-B O 

O O FOOD-B O 
O O FOOD-B O 

O O O O FOOD-B O O 
O O O O FOOD-B O O 

FOOD-B O O O FOOD-B O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O 
FOOD-B O O O FOOD-B O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O 

O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O 
O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O 

O O NOH-B O FOOD-B 
O O NOH-B O FOOD-B 

O FOOD-B O O O FOOD-B O 
O FOOD-B O O O FOOD-B O 

FOOD-B O O O O 
FOOD-B O O O O 

FOOD-B O O O 
FOOD-B O O O 

FOOD-B O O 
FOOD-B O O 

O O FOOD-B O PER-B O O O 
O O FOOD-B O PER-B O O O 

FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O POH-B O O 
FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O POH-B O O 

O O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O NOH-B NOH-I O O 
O O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O NOH-B NOH-I O O 

O FOOD-B O O O O 
O FOOD-B O O O O 

O FOOD-B O O NOH-B NOH-I O 
O FOOD-B O O NOH-B NOH-I O 

ORG-B O ORG-B O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O 
ORG-B O ORG-B O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O 

FOOD-B FOOD-I O FOOD-B O O DUR-B O O 
FOOD-B FOOD-I O FOOD-B O O DUR-B O O 

O O O O LOC-B FOOD-B O ORG-B O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O 
O O O O LOC-B FOOD-B O ORG-B O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O 

DAT-B DAT-I PER-B PER-I O PER-B ORG-B O FOOD-B O POH-B POH-B O O O 
DAT-B DAT-I PER-B PER-I O PER-B ORG-B O FOOD-B O POH-B POH-B O O O 

PER-B O NOH-B O PER-B O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O 
PER-B O NOH-B O PER-B O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O 

O O O O O O FOOD-B O O PER-B O O O O O O O O O 
O O O O O O FOOD-B O O PER-B O O O O O O O O O 

ORG-B ORG-I O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O 
ORG-B ORG-I O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O 

LOC-B O NOH-B O LOC-B O PER-B O O O O O O O O O FOOD-B O 
LOC-B O NOH-B O LOC-B O PER-B O O O O O O O O O FOOD-B O 

O ORG-B PER-B O O O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O 
O ORG-B PER-B O O O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O 

O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O FOOD-B NOH-B NOH-B O 
O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O FOOD-B NOH-B NOH-B O 

POH-B O O O O O FOOD-B O O 
POH-B O O O O O FOOD-B O O 

ORG-B FOOD-B O O O O FOOD-B O O O NOH-B O O O O DAT-B O 
ORG-B FOOD-B O O O O FOOD-B O O O NOH-B O O O O DAT-B O 

O O O NOH-B NOH-I FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B O O LOC-B O PER-B O O O PER-B O O O O 
O O O NOH-B NOH-I FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B O O LOC-B O PER-B O O O PER-B O O O O 

PER-B O O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O 
PER-B O O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O 

O DAT-B O O O O FOOD-B FOOD-I O FOOD-B O MNY-B PNT-B O MNY-B O DAT-B ORG-B O O O O O FOOD-B MNY-B 
O DAT-B O O O O FOOD-B FOOD-I O FOOD-B O MNY-B PNT-B O MNY-B O DAT-B ORG-B O O O O O FOOD-B MNY-B 

O O O O O O O O O PNT-B O O O O O NOH-B NOH-I O LOC-B NOH-B FOOD-B O O FOOD-B O 
O O O O O O O O O PNT-B O O O O O NOH-B NOH-I O LOC-B NOH-B FOOD-B O O FOOD-B O 

O PER-B PER-B O O O FOOD-B O O O O 
O PER-B PER-B O O O FOOD-B O O O O 

O LOC-B O O FOOD-B O ORG-B O O O 
O LOC-B O O FOOD-B O ORG-B O O O 

PNT-B O FOOD-B O O FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O 
PNT-B O FOOD-B O O FOOD-B FOOD-B FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O 

FOOD-B O O O O O O POH-B O O 
FOOD-B O O O O O O POH-B O O 

FOOD-B O O O FOOD-B O FOOD-B O O 
FOOD-B O O O FOOD-B O FOOD-B O O 

LOC-B LOC-I O O O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O O O O O O O O O 
LOC-B LOC-I O O O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O O O O O O O O O 

FOOD-B O O NOH-B O O O O O O O O O 
FOOD-B O O NOH-B O O O O O O O O O 

O O PER-B O O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O O O O 
O O PER-B O O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O O O O 

PNT-B LOC-B FOOD-B FOOD-I FOOD-I O O PER-B O O O O O O O O O 
PNT-B LOC-B FOOD-B FOOD-I FOOD-I O O PER-B O O O O O O O O O 

O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O DAT-B O DAT-B O FOOD-B FOOD-B 
O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O DAT-B O DAT-B O FOOD-B FOOD-B 

O O O O O O O O O O O O O O NOH-B O O O O O O O O FOOD-B 
O O O O O O O O O O O O O O NOH-B O O O O O O O O FOOD-B 

PER-B O O MNY-B O FOOD-B O O O O ORG-B O O O 
PER-B O O MNY-B O FOOD-B O O O O ORG-B O O O 

O FOOD-B NOH-B NOH-B O O 
O FOOD-B NOH-B NOH-B O O 

PER-B O PER-B O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O PER-B O O O O 
PER-B O PER-B O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O PER-B O O O O 

FOOD-B O FOOD-B PNT-B FOOD-B PNT-B FOOD-B PNT-B FOOD-B PNT-B O O O O PNT-B O O 
FOOD-B O FOOD-B PNT-B FOOD-B PNT-B FOOD-B PNT-B FOOD-B PNT-B O O O O PNT-B O O 

O PER-B FOOD-B FOOD-I O O O 
O PER-B FOOD-B FOOD-I O O O 

ORG-B PER-B O O NOH-B O O FOOD-B O 
ORG-B PER-B O O NOH-B O O FOOD-B O 

PER-B O O O O O FOOD-B O O POH-B LOC-B O O 
PER-B O O O O O FOOD-B O O POH-B LOC-B O O 

O FOOD-B NOH-B NOH-B O O 
O FOOD-B NOH-B NOH-B O O 

PER-B O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O O O O O O O O O O O 
PER-B O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O O O O O O O O O O O 

LOC-B LOC-B O O FOOD-B O O O 
LOC-B LOC-B O O FOOD-B O O O 

ORG-B NOH-B O FOOD-B O 
ORG-B NOH-B O FOOD-B O 

O PER-B O DAT-B O ORG-B O POH-B POH-I O O O O O O O O O FOOD-B FOOD-B O O O O O 
O PER-B O DAT-B O ORG-B O POH-B POH-I O O O O O O O O O FOOD-B FOOD-B O O O O O 

O PER-B O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O 
O PER-B O O FOOD-B O O O O O O O O O O O O 

O O LOC-B LOC-I O O O O FOOD-B O O LOC-B O O O O O 
O O LOC-B LOC-I O O O O FOOD-B O O LOC-B O O O O O 

POH-B POH-I O O O O O O O O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O 
POH-B POH-I O O O O O O O O FOOD-B FOOD-I O O 

DAT-B FOOD-B O O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O 
DAT-B FOOD-B O O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O 

O O O O O O FOOD-B O ORG-B O O O O O O MNY-B MNY-I O FOOD-B O O O O O O O 
O O O O O O FOOD-B O ORG-B O O O O O O MNY-B MNY-I O FOOD-B O O O O O O O 

O O O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O ORG-B O O O O O O 
O O O O O O O O O FOOD-B O O ORG-B O O O O O O 

O ORG-B DUR-B O FOOD-B O O NOH-B O O O MNY-B MNY-I O O 
O ORG-B DUR-B O FOOD-B O O NOH-B O O O MNY-B MNY-I O O 

FOOD-B O O O NOH-B O O O O O 
FOOD-B O O O NOH-B O O O O O 

O FOOD-B O O O O O O NOH-B NOH-I MNY-B O O 
O FOOD-B O O O O O O NOH-B NOH-I MNY-B O O 

O PER-B O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O PER-B O O O PER-B O PER-B O 
O PER-B O O O O FOOD-B O O O O O PER-B O O O PER-B O PER-B O 

O O FOOD-B NOH-B MNY-B FOOD-B MNY-B FOOD-B MNY-B 
O O FOOD-B NOH-B MNY-B FOOD-B MNY-B FOOD-B MNY-B 

FOOD-B FOOD-I MNY-B O O O O O O O 
FOOD-B FOOD-I MNY-B O O O O O O O 

O O O FOOD-B 
O O O FOOD-B 

